In a data center, a few hours before launch…
It’s hopeless. We won’t make it!
What am I going to do?
Azu, you look like you’re in trouble.
Let me help you!
Claudia!
Initializing startup sequence.
All hosts booted.
Network agents online.
All systems green.
All hosts booted.
Network agents online.
Windows Azure,
system launch.
Azu, now!
We did it, Azu!
Yeah, we did!
Windows Azure, Japan Data Center: Start!
Claudia Madobe
Eri Kitamura
Ruri Azumi
Kanae Itou
Production
Point Pictures
Animation
Yuuji Asao (Point Pictures)
Director
Morinaka Hikohito (Techno-Alliance Corp.)
Producer
Shinichiro Isago (Microsoft Japan)
Executive Production
Techno-Alliance Corp.
Writer
Microsoft Japan